The way you crushed Mike at Ping-Pong was such a turn-on. You wanna..?
噢，你用乒乓球打败麦克真的太帅了。 你想要……?
You know, I'd love to, but I'm a little tired.
呃，我是想，不过我有点累了
- I'll put a pillowcase over my head. - You're on.
- 我会用枕套把头包住的。 - 那来吧！
- Hey. - What's up?
- 嗨！ - 有事吗？
Well, Mike's taking a shower, which, by the way, there's no law against.
麦克在冲凉 顺便说一下，我们还没有做那个...
And then we're gonna grab some food. So if you want..
我想去吃点东西，所以如果你们也想……
- Finally. - Is that Ross?
那是罗斯吗？
Yeah. You can hear everything through these stupid walls.
是啊，那面破墙什么声音都包不住。
- Sounds like he's with someone. - He could be alone.
- 好象有人和他一起。 - 应该没有吧
This morning I heard him do pushups and then talk to his triceps.
今天早上我听见他做俯卧撑 后来还跟他的三头肌说话。
Wait a minute, I think Phoebe's right.
等等，我想菲比是对的。
Yeah, I hear someone else in there with him.
我也听见有人和他在一起。
- Dr. Geller! - God, you're amazing.
- 盖勒博士！ - 天呐，太不可思议了……
I didn't even have to ask you to call me that.
我刚想让你这样称呼我呢。
- Oh, my God, that's Charlie! - She's cheating on Joey with Ross!
- 噢，天呐，是查莉！ - 他背着乔伊和罗斯乱搞！
Oh, that tart! Floozy! Giant!
噢，那个尖酸刻薄的……大……荡妇……
- I'm not sure about this. - Yeah, you're right.
- 我不应该这样 - 对，你是对的。
This is none of our business.
这根本不关我们的事。
I'm not sure it's the best way to hear everything. Get me a glass!
不，我应该找个方法好好的偷听。 给我个玻璃杯！
No, I'm not gonna do this, okay? I'm not gonna eavesdrop on my friend.
噢，我不会那么做的。 我不会偷听我朋友的。
I love Barbados.
噢……我爱巴贝多！
I can't believe I'm kissing you. I'm kissing Rachel!
噢……我不敢相信我在吻你。 我在吻瑞秋啊！
I know. I'm her.
我知道，我就是她！
Rachel and Joey! It's Rachel and Joey!
瑞秋和乔伊！是瑞秋和乔伊！！！
- What? - Get over here!
- 什么？ - 过来这边！
Oh, my God! I love how thin these walls are!
噢，天呐，我喜欢这些薄墙！
Thank you.
谢谢。
The One After Joey And Rachel Kiss
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
Hey, before, you said that nothing could happen between us. What changed?
嘿，之前你说我们是不可能的 为什么又改变主意了？
Well, I only said that because of Ross.
之前这样说是因为罗斯...
- And then I saw him kissing Charlie. - What?
- 可后来我看见他在吻查莉…… - 什么？
Ross and Charlie?
罗斯和查莉？
Wow! She's really making her way through the group, huh?
哇！ 她真的很想加入到我们中来呢，呃？
- Eh, who am I to talk? - Yeah.
- 啊，说这个干吗？ - 啊....
I can't believe this. Rachel and Joey?
真不敢相信，瑞秋和乔伊？
How about the dinosaur twins in the other room?
那边那对恐龙二人组怎么办啊？
- No one is manning that wall! - I'm on it!
- 那堵墙没人负责啊！ - 有我呢！
- Anything? - I think I hear curtains closing.
- 听到什么了？ - 我想我听见他们在拉窗帘……
We've got shoes being kicked off over here.
我们听到鞋被踢掉了
Bedsprings! Unmistakable!
弹簧床，不会错的！
- You realize that's your brother. - Not until you said it. Somebody switch!
- 你有想过那是你哥吗？ - 你说出来才想到。找个人来换我啊！
Wow! Wait a minute.
等等！
Ross and Charlie. Joey and Rachel.
罗斯和查莉，乔伊和瑞秋，
Phoebe and Mike. We're the only ones leaving with the person we came with!
菲比和麦克！我们是唯一没有换过人的一对呢！
That's not true. I came with Monica, I'm leaving with Weird Al.
不是啊！我和莫妮卡一起来的 却要和古怪阿尔一起走。
Okay, I've had it with the hair jokes.
好吧，我受够了这种头发的笑话了。
- Tomorrow I'm going to the salon. - Okay, Buckwheat.
- 明天早上，我们走之前我会去发廊的。 - 好的，荞麦人！
You gotta hear this, it's great! It's like free porn.
你们该来听听这个，太棒了…… 简直就像是免费的A片！
- Is everything okay? - It's just.. I don't think I can do this.
- 呃……怎么啦？ - 对，只是……我想我不能这么做……
Oh, is it because of what might be on the bed?
噢……是否因为躺在床罩上？
- I saw that report, with the infrared.. - No! No.
- 我也看过那些报道了，在红外线下和... - 不，不！
No.
不。
Look, I need to talk to Joey. I mean, you guys just broke up.
呃，我要跟乔伊谈谈。 你们才刚刚分手。
Before anything more happens between us, I need to know he's okay with it.
我们之间再发生什么之前 我要确定他不反对。
- I completely understand. - All right, I'm gonna go find him.
- 我，呃……我完全明白。 - 好吧，我想我要去找他了……
I just need a second before I can, you know..
我想……我需要点时间…让我那个……
Grandma, Grandma, Grandma.
外婆…外婆…外婆…
- Okay, I'll see you later. - Okay!
- 好了，过会儿见。 - 好的……
That's the door. He's gone.
关门声，他走了……
And she's turning on the TV..
而她……打开了电视……
and watching Miss Congeniality.
在看……《选美特工》。
Honey? If you know it through a wall, you know it too well.
亲爱的，如果你连这都听得到 那你知道的就太多了！
Hey, what are you guys doing?
嘿，你们干什么呢？
We're just.. We're sad to go, so we're just saying goodbye to the hotel.
噢，我们在…… 快要走了，我们很伤心 所以在跟这旅馆告别。
I love you..
我爱你……
Paradise Hotel Golf Resort and Spa.
天堂旅店 高尔夫胜地和水浴……
Yeah. We had a great time, thank you.
对，我们玩得很开心，谢谢！
Bye.
再见！
Okay. Hey, have you guys seen Joey anywhere?
OK, 呃…… 嗨，你们看见乔伊在哪儿了吗？
He's probably in his room with his current girlfriend, Charlie.
他应该现在在他房间里 和他现任女友查莉在一起。
That's the situation as we know it.
这就是我们知道的情况……
If you see him, could you tell him I'm looking for him?
好吧，如果看到他，告诉他我在找他好吗？
- You got it. - Thanks.
- 没问题！ - 谢了！
Thank you.
谢谢你！
Other wall, people! Other wall!
另一边墙，伙计！另一边！
- Rach, you there? - Oh, my God, that's Ross!
- 瑞秋，你在吗？ - 噢，天呐，是罗斯啊。
- What are we gonna do? - Okay, just be calm.
- 怎么办？ - 噢，保-保-保持镇静。保持镇静。
For all he knows, we're just hanging out.
我们只是随便聊聊。
All right? So just be nonchalant.
好吗？ 随意一点。
- That's not nonchalant! - No idea what it means.
- 这不叫随意！ - 我不知道那是什么意思。
Okay, just hide.
哦……好吧，躲起来！
- Rach? - Coming! Try under the bed.
- 瑞秋? - 来了！试试床下行不行！
There's no room under the bed..
床底不够高啊。
- Is everything okay? - Yeah.
- 出什么事了？ - 没……
- Hey. Do you know where Joey is? - Hi.
- 嘿。     - 嗨… - 你知道乔伊在那儿吗？
I really don't.
我真的不知道……
- Can I talk to you for a minute? - Yeah. Sure.
- 我能和你谈谈吗？ - 当然，可以……
I don't believe this. Have you guys been..?
我简直不敢相信……你们一直……
This is the listening side of the wall.
嘘嘘……趴在墙上好好听。
Then she told me that she and Joey had broken up..
然后她告诉我她和乔伊分手了
and part of the reason was she had feelings for me.
某程度上是因为她对我有感觉。
Right. Yeah.
呃呃……对……没错……
You know I've wanted to ask Charlie out since the day I met her.
你知道吗，我碰到查莉 的那天就想约她出去。
Oh, I know, I know. That's been really hard for you.
噢，我明白……我知道这对你来说很难。
Anyway, one thing led to another, and..
不管怎么样，事情一件接一件，而且……
before you know it, we were kissing.
噢……还没知道是怎么回事，我们接吻了。
How angry do you think Joey's gonna be?
你觉得乔伊会多生气？
That is hard to say, Ross. That is hard to say.
这很难说，罗斯。这很难说。
I gotta find him. He's gotta be here someplace.
我要去找他了。他一定就在什么地方。
You would think.
就是啊！
Joey?
乔伊!
- Is he gone? - How are you doing this?
- 他走了吗？ - 你怎么做到的？
What? Hey!
怎么……哇……嘿！
What are you..? What is this? Have you been listening this entire time?
你们怎么……这是怎么回事？ 你们一直听着吗？
Yeah!
对！
Now, what is this?
那，这又是怎么回事？
What is this? Well, let's see. We kissed for 10 minutes..
啊，这是怎么回事？ 好吧，这么说吧 我们吻了十分钟
and now we're talking to our friends about it, so I guess this is sixth grade.
然后现在和朋友说这件事 我想只有六年级学生才这样！
No, no. Have you thought about how complicated this could get?
哦，不……你想过这会变得多复杂吗？
- What about Ross? - Well, he's with Charlie now.
- 罗斯怎么办? - 可他现在跟查莉在一起。
Yeah, but he wants to talk to you before anything really happens with her.
对，可他想在正式开始之前先和你说一下。
And as his friend, I mean, don't you think he deserves the same from you?
作为朋友，你们不觉得你们也应该这么做吗？
You're a pain in my ass, Geller.
你戳到我痛处了，盖勒兄妹！
Look, we appreciate all the advice..
好吧，很感谢你们的意见
but this is between Joey and me. We can handle it.
但这是我和乔伊之间的事，我们能处理……
We'll go. Will you do one thing for us, the people that care about you?
好吧，我们要回去了，可你能帮我们做件事吗？ 为这些在乎你们的朋友...
- Sure. - Enunciate.
- 当然…… - 去说清楚！
Get out!
出去！
Are they right?
你觉得怎样？
Probably, yeah. I mean, maybe we should..
可能吧，是…… 我是说
hold off until we talk to Ross.
我们应该先和罗斯说清楚。
Yeah. Yeah. We can wait. We don't have to do anything tonight.
对……对，我们可以等 我们今天晚上什么事都不做。
Yeah, I think that would be best.
对，我想这样最好……
So, I'm gonna.. I'm gonna take off.
那么，那么我要……我要走了……
- Although.. - I like "although."
- 除非…… - 我喜欢“除非”！
I mean, you know..
我是说
Ross and I haven't dated in, like..
我和罗斯已经有将近……
six years.
6年没约会了。
Six years?
6年？
Wow. That's almost as long as high school.
哇……跟读高中一样久了……
Plus, you know, he is with Charlie now.
而且，他现在跟查莉在一起。
Absolutely.
就是啊！
- He's not thinking about you. - No.
- 他已经对你没感觉了。 - 是啊。
I'm thinking about you.
我才对你有感觉...
Yeah.
对……
- Let's forget about Ross. - It's forgotten.
- 我们忘了罗斯吧…… - 已经忘了。
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
-怎么了？ - 没事……
Seriously, what is it?
说真的……怎么了？
Nothing. It's really.. It's nothing. Come here. Come here.
没事……真的…… 没事……再来……再来……
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Sorry, I just..
对不起，我只是，呃……
I can't seem to get Ross out of my head.
看起我来无法忽略罗斯……
Well, maybe I can help.
好吧，让我来帮你忙吧。
Your lips are so soft. Do that again.
哦，你的唇真软……再来一次……
Yeah, we need to talk to Ross. Yeah.
你说得对……我们真的要跟罗斯谈谈……
Hey. You guys ready to go?
嗨！你们准备好要走了？
Not quite. Monica's at the salon, and I'm finishing packing.
还没。莫妮卡还在发廊，而我还没收拾好。
Dude, you're not taking your Bible?
伙计！你不打算带上你的圣经吗？
You're not supposed to take that.
你不应该拿这个走的。
Besides, it's a New Testament. What are you gonna do with it?
而且这是新约，你要它干什么？
Learn about Jesus.
了解耶稣……
- Hey! - So did you talk to Joey?
- 嗨！ - 你跟乔伊说过了？
No. I couldn't find him. I'm just gonna talk to him on the plane.
呃，没……还没。我找不到她。 我会在飞机上跟他说。
Okay. Sounds like a good idea, Dr. Geller.
对，听起来不错……盖勒博士！
Stop it.
别这么说！
Ph.D.
PHD
You're filthy.
你真淫荡！
- Hey. Have you guys seen Monica? - Actually, I think she went to the salon.
- 嘿，你们见过莫妮卡了吗？ - 呃，我想她去发廊了。
Oh, yeah. Oh, she went to the salon, all right.
哦，对，噢，她刚去了发廊……
Check it out!
看一下！
Whose day just got better?
谁会最喜欢这个啊？
Chandler!
钱德！
Hey!
嘿!... 啊啊啊!
- What do you think? - I think..
- 你觉得怎么样？ - 我想……
I think I can see your scalp.
我想我能看见你的头皮。
Don't you just love it?
你不喜欢吗？
Yeah. Yeah, you got shellfish in your head.
对……对……对……你把贝壳挂在头上。
It's something. You go, girlfriend.
真是太……那个了……去吧，女生！
- You never said that in your life. - Not once.
- 你以前没这么说过是吗？ - 不止一次。
I thought so.
我想也是。
- Phoebe? - I'm so glad you did that.
- 菲比？ - 很高兴你这样做了！
Oh, and listen to this.
听听这个……
What do you know? It's a treat for the eyes and the ears.
你知道吗？…这真是对视觉...和听觉的享受。
Wow, it's kind of weird that I'm sitting next to Charlie after we broke up.
哦，噢。哇, 我和查莉分手后还要坐在她旁边，太尴尬了。
Yeah. It's almost as if Air Barbados doesn't care about your social life.
就是说，巴贝多航空真是不关心你的私生活。
Does someone mind switching and sitting with Charlie?
嘿，有人想替我跟查莉坐吗？
Oh, I mean, I.. Dude, I spent the whole conference with Charlie.
我……嘿！伙计，我跟查莉整个会议都混在一起了。
- I understand. - No, I'll do it.
- 我了解…… - 不，我要的。
Wish I could switch. I really don't want to sit with Allen lverson over there.
我也想跟谁换换。  我真的不想跟阿伦.艾佛森（篮球明星）坐在那儿。
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嘿！ - 嘿！
Once we're in the air and the captain turns off the seat belt sign..
呃……知道吗，当我们升空 机长关闭系好保险带的标志后……
you feel free to roam about my cabin.
你就可以自由的在我的小屋里遨游了……
And you should be careful when checking your overhead bins.
你检查行李箱的时候要小心
- Because items may shift during.. - Oh, you're not good at this.
- 很容易和别人的搞混的... - 啊……这个你不在行……
- Do you have to go home tonight? - No, I think I could come over.
- 今天晚上你非要回家吗？ - 不，我想我可以来过夜的。
It's Saturday, right?
今天星期六，不是吗？
What?
怎么了？
- I can't do anything tonight. - Why not?
- 呃……今晚我不行。 - 为什么？
I have a date.
我有约会。
- You have a date? With who? - Oh, it's my girlfriend.
- 你有个……你有个约会？跟谁？ - 噢，是……我女朋友。
- You have a girlfriend? - Yeah.
- 你有……你有女朋友？ - 对……呃
Well, when you and I broke up, I started seeing someone.
之前我们分手后，我开始约会其他人。
- Well, for how long? - Three months.
- 那...多久了？ - 3个月。
Three months?
3个月?
Okay.
好吧……
This is none of my business, but how long are you gonna keep seeing her?
这可能不关我的事, 只是 呃……你认为你还会跟她好多久？
I'll tell her that it's over tonight at dinner. I promise.
今天晚上晚饭的时候，我会告诉她结束了。 我保证。
Oh, okay, good. You do that.
噢，好吧……好的。那你去吧。
When you get home, maybe there'll be a special delivery package waiting for you.
然后当你回到家 可能会有个特别的邮包在那儿等着你。
Maybe I'll sign for it, tear it open.
我可能会签收。撕开它。
- Pull out the packing material.. - We'll have sex. Let's leave it there.
- 扯开包装材料……. - 你知道吗，我们会做爱。你不用再说了
It's our last glimpse of Barbados.
这是我们看巴贝多的最后一眼了！
And my last glimpse of anything.
也是我看世间万物的最后一眼。
All right, I'm gonna go talk to Joey. I think this is the right time.
好吧，我要去和乔伊谈谈。 我想现在是时候了。
He's in a good mood after the flight attendant says "duty-free."
空姐说完“duty free”(免税)以后他总是情绪很好。 [注：乔伊听成doody free（随便做）了]
Okay. Good luck.
好，祝你好运！
You know, if he's not okay with this then nothing more can happen between us.
你知道, 如果他不能接受那我们之间就什么都不能发生
I know.
我知道。
Well, if that's the case, I just want you to know..
恩, 如果事情真的那样了我想让你知道...
that I think I could have fallen for you really, really hard.
我认为我可能已经爱你非常非常深了
On the other hand, if he is okay with us..
另一方面来说, 如果他能接受
then, you know, it's cas, whatever.
那就...你知道...算了, 管他呢
Ross is coming over. I think now would be a good time to talk to him.
罗斯要过来了。 我想现在会是个告诉他的好时候。
I guess so. I'm just.. I'm really nervous.
我想是的。只是……我好紧张啊。
Well, keep in mind that by the time you're done..
好吧，你这样想着： 你说完以后
they'll probably be serving dinner.
他们就上餐了。
Still nervous?
还紧张吗？
I'm gonna get the lasagna.
我要吃宽面条。
- Hey, Rach? - Yeah?
- 嗨，瑞秋…… - 怎么！
- Do you mind if I sit here for a sec? - Yeah. Yeah, sure. Yeah.
- 介意我在这儿坐一会吗？ - 不介意，当然不！不！
Good luck.
祝你好运！
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
So I..
我，呃……
I kind of need to talk to you about Charlie.
有点儿关于查莉的事要跟你说。
- Yeah? - Last night, after you guys broke up..
- 怎么？ - 好吧，昨天晚上你们俩分手以后……
So sorry to hear about that, by the way.
当然我觉得很遗憾…… 呃
Well, Charlie and I were talking, and..
查莉和我倾诉，然后……
Well..
呃
You kissed.
你们接吻了。
Wh.. What?
哇……什么？
What? What would give you that idea?
你怎么会这样想的啊？
- I saw you. - Yeah, we kissed.
- 我看见了。 - 对，我们是接吻了
But nothing else. Nothing else happened, okay?
不过…什么都没发生，知道吗。
- Ross, Ross, Ross. It's okay. - What?
- 罗斯……没关系的。 - 什么？
It's okay. You know, look..
这没关系。
I totally understand, all right? You guys..
我完全理解，好吗？ 你们...
make way more sense than her and I ever did, you know? And..
你比我更适合她。你知道吗？ 而且……
- I want you to be happy. - Are you serious?
- 我希望你们幸福。 - 真的？
Yeah.
当然……
- Now I have something.. - I am speechless.
- 我也有点事想说…… - 我真是无话可说了……
I mean, the fact that you would put my happiness first like that, I mean..
你居然把我的幸福放在第一位。 我是说...
You're an incredible friend, do you know that?
你真是个令人难以置信的好朋友 你知道吗？
- Well, look, before you go.. - No, I mean it.
- 噢……呃……呃……在你…… - 不，我说真的。
I mean, you're so loyal, man. And selfless and generous.
你既忠诚，又无私，慷慨……
I am those things, yeah.
我是，当然是。
I've known Chandler longer, so I think of him as my best friend. But now..
你知道吗？我认识钱德更久 我也一直把他作为我最好的朋友
I may have to rethink some stuff.
不过现在…… 我想应该重新考虑一下了……
Dude!
伙计！
Hey, if there is ever anything I can do for you..
嘿，有没有事情我能帮忙的？
I can't think of anything.
暂时还没有……
- Thanks. - Yeah.
- 谢谢！ - 没什么！
- So hi. - Hi.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
- So you talked to Joey? - Oh, yeah. We had a really good talk.
- 你，呃，你和乔伊谈过了？ - 啊，对。我们聊得很开心。
- Oh, that's great. - Yeah.
- 噢！太棒了！ - 对！
- So everything's okay? - Oh, no, it's great.
- 噢，一切都好吗？ - 噢，不，简直太棒了。
- It's great. He's an amazing guy. - Oh, well, obviously, I think so too.
- 太棒了。他真是……他真是好得让人吃惊。 - 啊……呃，显然我也这么想。
Well, I'm so excited about this.
对，我感到很兴奋。
Really? Excited?
真的？兴奋？
What, are you kidding? I have had some very dirty dreams about this.
你开玩笑吗？我现在做梦 都在想着要去干那事……
Excuse me.
让开！
You didn't tell him, did you?
你没说是吗？
I couldn't. He was saying all these really nice things about me.
我没法说。他把我说得天花乱坠。
I didn't want him to get mad and take them back. I'm gonna edge out Chandler!
我不想惹火他，收回他说的话。  我快要顶替钱德的位置了。
Fine. Forget it. When we go back to New York, I will tell him.
好吧，好吧！回纽约以后，我跟他说。
Thank you. Yeah, I appreciate that.
谢谢。真的，我跟感激。
- Hi, Mike's place. - Hey, it's Mike.
- 嗨，麦克家。 - 嘿，是麦克。
- That was fast. - Oh, no, she's not here yet.
- 噢，真快。 - 噢，呃……不，她还没来。
You know, I'm just gonna take off and break up with her over the phone.
知道吗，我想我应该走了 我可以在电话上跟她说分手。
You can't do that. Oh, come on, Mike, strap on a pair.
不，你不能走！快用东西捆住自己！
Why don't you tell her that we got back together. Women appreciate honesty.
你为什么不直接告诉她我们又在一起了。 知道吗，女人欣赏诚实。
We also appreciate gentle spanking once in a while, just FYl.
也喜欢轻柔的拍打。
One more thing. There might be a picture of Precious on my coffee table.
还有一件事……  可能……在我的咖啡台上有张Precious的照片。
Her name's Precious?
她叫Precious（珍贵）?
Is she a pure breed, or did you pick her up at the pound?
她是纯种的吗？ 你在兽笼里挑的她？
- I just want to give you a heads up. - Okay. And if she gets upset..
- 不管怎么说，我只想让你知道一下。 - 好吧，噢，如果她伤心的话
just scratch her tummy and give her a liver snap.
记得挠挠她的肚子，逗她高兴
What do you know, another hot blonde.
你知道吗 又一个金发女郎。
Hi. I'm Precious. Who are you?
嗨，我是Precious，你是谁？
- I'm Phoebe. - Phoebe?
- 我……我是菲比。 - 菲比？
Mike's ex-girlfriend, Phoebe? The love of his life? That Phoebe?
麦克的前女友菲比？ 他一生所爱的？那个菲比？
Oh, I can't wait for everyone at work to see these!
噢，我真想快让同事们快点看看这个……嗷！
- You go back to work tomorrow night? - Yeah.
- 明天晚上你就要回去工作了是吗？ - 对！
So if you want people to see them..
那么如果你想让他们看
you're not having them taken out, say, at the break of dawn?
也就是说你今晚不会把他们解下啦？
Well, if I had them taken out, then I wouldn't be able to do this.
呃，如果我解下来了，我就不能这么做了。
You like that, right?
你喜欢的，是吗？
- What are you singing? - It's "Bolero" from 10.
- 你唱什么呢？ - 《十全十美》里的波利乐舞曲。
It's "Ride of the Valkyries" from Apocalypse Now.
那是《现代启示录》里的《狂热的瓦格纳》。
Here's the thing. The cornrows were a solution to your frizzy-hair problem.
事情是这样的：这些贝壳是用来解决 你头发的卷曲问题的。
Now that we're home, you don't have that problem. If you think about it..
而现在我们回家了，我们不再受那个问题困扰了 所以如果你考虑一下……
I hate them.
我讨厌他们！
- What? You said you liked them. - Did I? Let's refresh.
- 什么？你说过你喜欢的。 - 我说过吗？我们回想一下。
I believe what I said was that I could see your scalp.
我想我说的是“我可以看见你的头皮”。
Well, fine. So you don't like them. Everybody else does.
好吧，那么你不喜欢。可其他人都喜欢。
Again, let's journey back.
再想想，让我们想回到那次旅游……
As I recall, Rachel said she had never noticed the shape of your skull before.
我记得瑞秋说的是 她以前从没注意过你的头骨的形状。
And Joey? Well, Joey didn't realize there was anything different.
还有乔伊…… 乔伊当时看不出你有什么不一样。
You know what? I don't care. I like it, and I'm gonna keep it.
知道吗？我不管。 我喜欢这样，喜欢它，而且我要留着它。
You're just jealous because your hair can't do this.
你嫉妒是因为你的头发不能这么做……嗷！
- Get yourself in the tooth? - And the eye.
- 敲在你的牙上了？ - 还有眼睛！
Hi! There she is! Hi, Emma. Oh, my God, I missed you.
嗨……她来了。嗨,艾犸。 噢，天呐，我想死你了。
Oh, Emma, I missed you so much. Hi.
哦，艾犸，我真是太想你了，嗨！
Did you have a good time with Grandma Greene? Huh?
嘿……你和姥姥过得开心吗？呃？
Did she give you a bottle of antidepressants again to use as a rattle?
她喋喋不休的时候给你兴奋剂了吗？
That was one time, Ross, and they were only, like, five milligrams.
只有一次，罗斯，而且只有5毫克。
Hey, Emma, Daddy has some presents for you, okay? I want you to wait right here.
噢，嘿，艾犸，爸爸有礼物带给你。 知道吗？ 我想让你在这儿等一会儿
Come here, sweetie.
等等，宝贝儿。
Ross, actually, there's something that I really need to talk to you about.
呃……罗斯 事实上我有点儿事要跟你说。
Okay, shoot.
好的，说吧！
- Okay. All right, here's the deal. - Oh, no!
- 好吧，呃……好的，事情是这样的。 - 哦不！
- What is it? - Oh, major shampoo explosion!
- 怎么了？那是什么？ - 噢，大瓶的洗发液破了！
- Look, Ross, this really isn't easy. - Oh, it's all over everything!
- 呃，听着罗斯，这很难开口。 - 啊！！还沾得到处都是。
Why? Why me?
为什么？为什么偏偏是我？
Because you took 300 bottles of shampoo?
因为你拿了300瓶洗发液？
I guess things were just going too well for me.
我猜这些东西对我来说太珍贵了.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You were saying?
对不起，对不起。你刚才说什么？
- Well, yeah. Look, it's about me and.. - Oh, not another one!
- 好吧，呃……好吧，听着，是关于我和…… - 噢，不要，又一瓶！？
Oh, my God.. Oh, and this is moisturizer! It's even harder to clean!
噢，天……是摩丝。这个更难清理！
Why? Why do bad things happen to good people?
为什么？为什么坏事总是落到好人的头上？
- Wow. Clearly this is not a good time. - You think?
- 哇！好吧，很显然这不是个好时候。 - 嗯，你觉得呢？！
Okay. Bye.
好的，再见。
All right, so Mike's on his way over.
好了，麦克已经回来了。
You thought you were meeting here, he thought at the restaurant, so..
知道吗，你以为你们在这儿见 他却以为在餐馆见面 所以……
It doesn't matter who's right or wrong. The point is, I'm gonna take off.
谁对谁错不重要 重要的是…… 我要走了。
Wait. I'm not letting you leave until you tell me what's going on. I mean..
你告诉我到底发生了什么之前 我不会让你走的。
are you guys getting back together or something?
我是说，你们和好了还是怎么了？
All right.
好吧……
Susie.. Can I call you Susie?
苏茜，我能叫你苏茜吗？
My name is Precious.
我叫Precious。
I can't say that.
对，可我叫不出口。
Susie, I'm gonna be straight with you.
呃……Susie，我想跟你直说……
Mike and I are back together. And unfortunately..
麦克和我和好了…… 并且，呃……不幸的是
that effectively ends your relationship with him.
这样就要终结你们的关系。
He's very sorry about that, and wishes you the best luck in all your endeavors.
并且他对此感到很抱歉，并祝你好运。
I just can't believe this. Why?
我无法相信……为什么？
- Well, I don't.. - Why would he do this?
- 这个我也不知…… - 噢，他为什么这么做？
- What's wrong with me? - There's nothing wrong with you.
- 我做错什么了？ - 没有，你什么也没做错。
What the hell am I supposed to do now?
我是说，现在我到底该做什么？
Damn it, woman! Pull yourself together!
可恶！你这女人，镇定点，镇定。
Have some pride, for the love of God!
保持你的尊严，看在上帝的份上！
Okay, not a fan of the tough love.
好吧，你好象不喜欢苦涩的爱情。
I just can't believe that Mike didn't give me any warning.
我真不明白，为什么他不给我点暗示在先呢！
He didn't know. He wasn't planning on coming to Barbados and proposing to me.
他之前也不知道的 他本来没计划到巴贝多向我求婚的……
He proposed to you? This is the worst birthday ever!
他向你求婚了？ 我这个生日真是糟透了。
Look, Precious..
听着，Precious……
Mike's not worth this. You're an attractive, intelligent woman..
你不值为麦克伤心。 你是个迷人的、聪明的女孩
and let's face it, Mike's kind of a wang.
你看 麦克简直有点混蛋。
He proposed to me while he was still seeing you.
我是说 他向我求婚的时候甚至还跟你在一起……
He was gonna break up with you on your birthday?
他居然想在你生日的时候跟你分手？
I don't like to kiss and tell, but he cheated on you a lot this weekend.
并且，我本来也不想说的 不过这个周末他对你不忠的太多了。
Oh, my God, you know, maybe you're right. Maybe I don't need him.
噢，天呐，可能你说对了。 可能我并不需要他。
I deserve to be treated with respect.
我应该受到尊重。
Screw you, Mike. You're a coward and a bastard, and I hope you rot in hell!
你这个混蛋，麦克。 你这个胆怯的杂种，我希望你烂死在地狱里。
You're welcome.
不用谢我！
Honey? You've been in there for a long time. Is everything okay?
亲爱的，你在里面好久了……没事吧？
Not really.
有一点事。
I have a problem.
我出事了。
Really? What happened?
是吗？怎么了？
Well, I was dancing around and singing "No Woman, No Cry"..
好吧，我唱着《No Woman, No Cry》跳舞...
and I got stuck.
然后就挂住了。
- You can't move at all? - Oh, I can move.
- 一点都动不了？ - 噢，不，我可以动……
If I untangle you, will you please get rid of the cornrows?
如果我解开你，你会解开这个稻穗头？
I guess so.
我想会……
- Some of these look a little frayed. - Yeah, I tried to gnaw myself free.
- 有些看起来缠在一起了。 - 对，我自己试着解开过。
- Hey. - Hi.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
- So? Did you tell Ross? - Well, I tried..
- 呃……你跟罗斯说了吗？ - 没有，我想说
but then he had a shampoo-related emergency.
但他的洗发液出事故了。
- So I guess now it's your turn again. - No, no, no, no.
- 所以我想该轮到你去了。 - 不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不……
I think it's better if you tell him. You know, it's easier for a woman.
我想最好是你去告诉他，知道吗  这对女人来说容易些。
That way, you know, if he gets mad, all you have to do is go:
你知道，如果他抓狂了 你就可以……
"I didn't mean it.
我不是有意的。
I'm so sorry."
我太抱歉了。
Yeah, because that's what we do.
对，我们的确会这么做的
All right, all right, okay. How about this? How about this? Tomorrow..
好吧，好吧，这样，呃……这样，这样怎么样？
Tomorrow we'll both go and we'll tell him together.
明天……明天我们一起去，一起告诉他。
Okay, that sounds fair.
好吧，听起来公平些。
- That just means, once again, we can't.. - I know.
- 可这样我们又不能…… - 我知道，我知道……
That's okay. I mean, we can control ourselves. We're not animals.
不过没问题。 我们有自制力，我们不是动物啊。
- No! Of course, we can wait. - Yeah.
- 当然，当然我们可以等。 - 是啊。
All right, so I guess that means good night then.
那么我想该说晚安了？
Yep. Good night.
好的！晚安！
Good night.
晚――安！
晚安！
- Seriously, good night. - Stop saying good night.
- 说真的，晚安！ - 别说晚安了。
I'm so sorry.
好的。真对不起啊...
Look what I found in the drawer.
看我在抽屉里找到了什么……
And you said I'd never wear this.
你还说我永远不会戴它呢。
Now that I untangled you, how about you do a little something for me?
我把你解救下来，你还没报答我呢？
- Sure. What did you have in mind? - I think you know.
-当然，你想让我怎么报答？ - 你应该知道的啊。
- Really? I don't.. I don't really feel like it. - This is what I want to do.
- 真的？但我有点不想啊。 - 我就是想要。
Okay.
好吧。
I just don't get why you like it so much.
我不知道你为什么这么喜欢它。
She's an FBI agent posing as a beauty contestant!
她是个FBI特工，还参加选美呢。